<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wrkr</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Debug</string>
    <string name="menu_help">Help</string>

    <string name="help_text"><b>Purpose</b>
        \n\nThis application is designed to keep your wrists and fingers active to help prevent
        a variety of health issues such as arthritis.

        \n\n\n<b>Requirements</b>
        \n\nYou will need, in addition to this application on your device, a smartwatch that
        can also run this application.  The smartwatch must contain an accelerometer sensor
        and must be worn on your left wrist.  The smartwatch should be bluetooth-paired with your
        phone and should remain around your phone when you are at a computer.
        A Google sign-in is required to synchronize your profile between the device and our web
        server, where you will be performing monitored wrist exercises.  A Leap Motion device
        will need to be connected to the device you are using our website on.

        \n\n\n<b>How it works</b>
        \n\nWhen we detect that you are at a keyboard, the accelerometer on the watch will be
        triggered in a service to batch collect as much data as needed to figure out how long
        you have been idle at the computer doing minimal exercise.  These calculations are done
        using advanced machine learning on your phone as to help preserve some of your watch\'s
        battery level.  When we notice you have been idle at a keyboard for about 30 minutes,
        your mobile device will give you a notification to consider an exercise.  When you open
        the app, a log of these notifications will be presented on the home screen.  You can
        swipe these away when you do not want to consider that warning to exercise.  When you
        are prompted for an exercise, simply log onto the wrkr website with your Google account
        and you will get a training plan that suits your activity levels.  Perform exercises
        above the Leap Motion device and we will track your progress.

        \n\n\n<b>Additional Information</b>
        \n\nThis application is a collaboration between Mike Stowell and Sergei Fomichev as
        part of the COMP.5800 Ubiquitious Computing course at the University of Massachusetts,
        Lowell.\n\n\n\n
    </string>
</resources>
